{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "If share prices (drop) ......... ...., we will lose our money.\n",
      "a": "drop",
      "b": "will drop",
      "c": "is dropping",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he (come) .......... before ten, we will meet him at the station.\n",
      "a": "is coming",
      "b": "wil come",
      "c": "comes",
      "answer": "3",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you (eat) ........... an apple every day, you'll be very healthy.\n",
      "a": "eat",
      "b": "will eat",
      "c": "are eating",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we (not protect) .......... the elephant, it will become extinct.\n",
      "a": "don't protect",
      "b": "won't protect",
      "c": "aren't protecting",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "She (look) ........... completely different if she cuts her hair.\n",
      "a": "look",
      "b": "will look",
      "c": "is looking",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "You will pay a higher insurance if you (buy) .......... a sports car.\n",
      "a": "buy",
      "b": "will buy",
      "c": "are buying",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "You (be able).......... to see better if you turn on the lamp.\n",
      "a": "are able",
      "b": "will be able",
      "c": "are being",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "You will get heart disease if you (eat)......... too much meat.\n",
      "a": "eat",
      "b": "will eat",
      "c": "are eating",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you (not put) ........... so much sugar in your coffee, you won't put on so much weight.\n",
      "a": "don't put",
      "b": "won't put",
      "c": "aren't putting",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If a deer (get) ......... into your garden, it will eat all your plants.\n",
      "a": "gets",
      "b": "will get",
      "c": "is getting",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "2"
    }
  ]
}